https://www.ampltd.com/privacy-policy/

1) How we collect information
When you browse the Advanced Micro Peripherals web site, you do so anonymously. Your personal information – including your e-mail address – is not collected. Your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) and domain are logged to have an idea of which parts of our website you are visiting and how much time you are spending there.
There are times when we may request that you voluntarily supply your personal information, including your name, e-mail address, and address, for purposes such as access to reserved areas, registering for a new product, correspondence, e-mail registration, or participating in an online survey. Once you choose to provide personal information by which you can be identified, you can be assured that it will only be used to support your customer relationship with Advanced Micro Peripherals.
On specific pages of the Advanced Micro Peripherals site, you can require specific services, make requests, download free software and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are name and contact information.
2) How we use information
The information we collect is used for internal review and it may be a great help in improving the content of our web site. We use your personal information to:
send you e-mails to communicate back to you and to update you about new products and services
make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once
help you quickly find software, services or information that is relevant to you
better understand your needs and provide you with better service
measure consumer interest in our services and products
3) Consent
Advanced Micro Peripherals will not use or share your personal information without first asking for your permission. Advanced Micro Peripherals will not sell, rent or lease your personal registration data to others.
4) Use of Cookies
This website uses its own “cookies” in order to enhance user-friendliness (“cookies” are data sets that are sent to the user’s browser from the web server, and are stored there for later recall). No personal data are stored in our own “cookies.” You can prevent the use of “cookies” in general if you disallow the storage of “cookies” in your browser.
5) Use of Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (‘Google’). Google Analytics uses ‘cookies,’ which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. In the event IP anonymization is activated on this website, your IP address will be shortened beforehand by Google within member states of the European Union or in other signatory states of the Treaty on the European Economic Area. The full IP address will be transmitted to a Google Server in the USA and shortened there only on an exceptional basis. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators, and providing other services to website operators relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google will not associate the IP address transmitted under Google Analytics by your browser with other data held by Google. You may prevent the storage of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser software; however, we must advise you that in this case, you might not be able to use all functions of this website to the full extent. You may prevent Google from recording the data generated by the cookie and pertaining to your use of the website (including your IP address), or processing these data by downloading and installing the following browser plug-in.
6) Use of Marketing Automation Software
We use marketing automation software from a third-party provider to record and evaluate the tracking profile of website visitors.
When you visit our websites, the marketing automation software records your click path and uses this to create an individual tracking profile under a pseudonym. Cookies that allow your browser to be recognized are used for this purpose.
You can deactivate the creation of pseudomized usage profiles at any time by configuring your Internet browser so that it does not accept cookies.
The tracking profiles created by our software are not merged with data about the holder of the pseudonym without your explicit consent.
If you give us your consent by activating the checkbox provided for this purpose, you consent to the following collection, processing and use of your personal data:
“I hereby consent to my personal click path on the website of Advanced Micro Peripherals being recorded and to it being collected, processed and used together with my personal information from the contact form. The aforementioned information will be recorded in a central database and will only be used for the purpose of individual information and consultation as well as for market research purposes.”
You may revoke your consent at any time, effective for the future. To do so, please send a mail to marketing@ampltd.com.
7) Third-party sites
You should be aware that when you are on the Advanced Micro Peripherals site, you may be directed to other sites operated by our affiliates or by third-party providers that are beyond our control. Some of these sites will have a separate privacy policy. Advanced Micro Peripherals cannot be responsible for the information policy practiced by these sites. It is your entire responsibility to check that these sites are bound by the appropriate confidentiality agreements before offering any of your personal information.
8) Children’s privacy
The Advanced Micro Peripherals site does not target children. We do not market to children and do not solicit data from them. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, the Advanced Micro Peripherals web site by visitors under 18 years of age without the consent of their parents.
9) Further Information and Contact
Please contact us if you have questions about this Data Privacy Statement. You can send a mail to marketing@ampltd.com. You can request if and which data we have stored about you, at any time. Furthermore, you can send us information, requests for deletion and corrections as well as suggestions by email to marketing@ampltd.com.
10) Your acceptance of these terms
By using this site, you signify your assent to the Advanced Micro Peripherals Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, do not use our site. We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions from this notice at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your use of the Advanced Micro Peripherals site following the posting of changes to these terms means that you accept these changes.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.
Enquiry (0)
Login
UK +44 1353 659 500
US +1 212 951 7205
Register Today to View Secure Documents
To view reference manuals and white papers, you must be a registered user. If you are not yet a member,
please create an account today! Registration typically takes less than one minute.
We care about your privacy. To learn how we use your data please read our
Croatia (Hrvatska)
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Iran (Islamic Republic of)
Slovakia (Slovak Republic)
Virgin Islands (British)
Virgin Islands (U.S.)
